I don't remember anything slow and every secret you don't show left behind still inside your mind
something's always watching you guys will have to do the wax melting thing next time but I have
these really cool hey what's up boom builder what's up what's up um yeah how was your guys day so
today was um a day um is it one is it Wednesday it's not even it's still Tuesday here seven seven
I was gonna do the horoscopes for the this is a portal day actually and
You know different people have done different ceremonies for their traditions. I think you know, it's pretty
Universal to have certain days. I think you know sevens usually kind of lucky number. That's 7-eleven and
70s of the week seven dwarfs. There's
I don't know. Anyway, there's seven castaways on Gilligan's Island, right?
Seven charge standard seven well, unfortunately, there's not seven people in the chat yet
When there's seven people in the chat, I'll start but hey got a couple drinks. I got a cigar. I got a copy
BRs charge in
Am I I think I look good? I mean, it's like I just keep here. I'm not like, you know
This is not like CGI or something. I just like I just shaved a little bit and like, you know
Put my hair back, but it's like right
According to these people like
I'm like, I look, I think Christine said I look like I'm, I'm 85 or 90 years old.
I mean, I think it's just a little bit, a little bit, a little bit of exaggerated free fire sales.
A sale is not free.
It's, it's heavily discounted, but free.
I might as well just shave my head for free.
Probably could use that.
Well, let's see how about we can do $3 or $5 fire sales.
Mm-hmm, but and then I'll I have like blinkers, but they can look have a much read out. It's like hardly anything in there
Like someone's gone a little bit in there a little bottom
I'm got that I
Don't know
You know you're gonna be told Christine and someone got into another fight. Well, I did hear
some of that I
I didn't quite know the whole context of it.
It seems like they have a long relationship
and sometimes friends will fight.
The true friendship will survive the fights.
But sometimes things are said and done,
sometimes that go too far.
And I'm not talking about them.
I'm talking about my situation.
She was live yesterday.
Yeah, she's been going to live a lot lately.
I see, go to Perry Page Wind and Wildflower Arts.
That's what it is and yeah, I want to subscribe she is and she's like you know more focused on like you know
Doing the free readings and stuff for people which I should but I'm just I have a you know
Too out of ADHD and I'm too much organized to get I need to like
And you get motivated so but hey, I always will do free free readings for three cards
But I have to be asked it has to be like kind of the right timing sometimes, but uh, let's get into the horoscope. So
So I hope you liked my
My image here, I'll put this as the image in the background and I'll put my thumbnails in my background image
It's an ode. I actually it's a kind of an ode to you know, it's a it's cancer is
77 it's you know cancer or in the we're in the astrological side of cancer
77 and when I think of cancer, you know, I think of my mother because you know
but I also think of Diana because cancers rule by the moon and so
Diana was
One of the first Virgin Mother energies you can see there's the crest of moon. There's a little
I don't know if there's a Masonic temple or something behind there, but I don't know but there she's with a big
I think it's pretty cool, but it's like kind of like based on Diana, which I think the real Mary is anyway
But I'll tell you I don't want to get too. She plays golf lives you
Right, you know what? But you know golf would it stands for it stands for gentlemen only ladies forbidden
So she's a rule breaker yet on page. I hear she's a witch, but I hear she's a good witch
unless you deserve to be turned into a toad.
Yeah, does anyone see in the movie, The Wicker Man?
Like, the other night I watched it and it was weird
because it's like, I just, I just get feelings to like,
oh, I don't, and that's like, it's not like,
I always get these feelings.
Like once it's the ones that we were always watching movies.
Things are coming to my head like oh like this one for some reason. I just didn't know why but I just bought my intuition
What look I look I have a green flame around me
So I watched the wicker man again, which I've seen I don't know if I've seen the Nicholas Cage one
But you know, I'm born the same same birth did Nicholas Cage and it's one seven which looks like that
Okay, a little bit looks like the pie symbol when it's crossed like that. I don't know
But it's also been like a number of sacrifice to I've heard
But it's also that this is the gateway though. So this is maybe a portal, but you hear Trump is in Turkey
And he was like doing some kind of like funeral procession or something like that
Didn't want to hear about this or no, but I don't know it seems like he was like
It's just there's a lot of weird stuff going on right now. We'll say that okay, so I'll do the horoscopes
That'll be something fun that everyone can enjoy and you know take something from oh
So but yeah, well
I wrote a song for a thing that is last night, I think it's my favorite, my new favorite song, I'm not even gonna have it, let me see if I have it, I think I'm gonna delete all my media today, and I did, okay, well, I can go grab it on the site, okay.
Yeah, I wrote a song about a thing that is and it's like I got to demonstrate kind of like
my you know, at least you know, it's like I I'm putting a lot of
information and things to make it funny and good and stuff like that. Not always perfect at the
mother goose stuff aspect of it, but I'm a good writer. I mean, I was in English honors class and I used to
Alright, I didn't used to love to read, I still love to read, but I used to like to read more, more like, you know, fantasy books and stuff, but now I've been really into non-fiction and like educational and stuff.
But, I want to see if I can grab it.
But shout out your sign in the chat, and uh, yeah, this is how you, I mean, it's pretty good where we're like, oh, it's 10, 17 right now, 77 here.
So it's a good day to like, you know, set an intention it's a gateway day and it's like, you know
You know what gateways are like, you know, there's there's two things that open and they close and so you need to
Kind of take advantage of it while it's here and
Get in the tune of it so you can walk through the gateway. Also, here's anything interesting. I heard
CERN closed the Hadron Collider like on the 29th or something and so
Some people think that the Hadron Collider was like responsible for weird goings on stuff in America and around the world, right?
But I probably was. Let me see.
Trump is presenting the World Cup trophy to the winner. Okay. Is that in Turkey? Your underwear smells like an omelette? What kind of omelette?
that pitted cheese and garlic?
That would be pretty disgusting.
But why does it smell like an omelet?
Did you sit on some eggs?
Are you ovulating?
Wouldn't that be disgusting if we ate period blood omelets?
And that'd be gross.
Cause we eat like every other kind of egg,
like you know, they're considered like chicken pieces.
And so I don't know, I don't want to be disgusting.
I'm so sorry.
Okay, here's the song.
Called, it's called You Weird
because Sam-Anne was on beat
It's a you weird man you weird you weird and then it was like you always keep saying it you weird you weird
We so that's why I knew you weird. It was like he does a really funny impression of Sam
Disappointed he's behind the drums keeping perfect time then starts another pointless argument online
technically
actually
historically speaking
Brother nobody
The drum solo becomes another debate
He's bald. He's handsome high collar every night
He's taking number drops is zero. Let's see. So let's get let's get the let's get to the uh, let's get to the fun stuff, right?
the
the horoscopes
Okay, so we start off with the you know, we're
the zodiac starts off with Aries, right?
That I'm gonna tell you.
So this is called the Black Mirror Gateway, okay?
So July 7th, the gateway on July 7th,
it's all the 77 gateway.
It symbolizes introspection, intuition, and transformation.
Whether viewed spiritually, psychologically,
or simply as a meaningful moment for reflection,
tonight's theme is the same.
The mirror reveals to you what you're ready to see.
So, if there's Aries in the room, Aries, you're first, and Aries love being first.
Your theme for the gateway is Master Your Fire.
The universe isn't asking you to fight harder, it's asking you to choose your battles wisely.
Old frustration surface, so they can finally be released.
Lead with courage, not impulse.
And your special message from the gateway is the strongest warrior knows when to lower the sword
Your power color
For the gateway is crimson
Okay, Taurus
The theme of your seven seven black mirror gateway is breaking old foundation
Something you've outgrown is becoming impossible to ignore.
What once felt safe may now feel confining.
Trust that making room for change creates space
for greater stability.
Your message is the strongest roots
will still welcome new growth.
And your power color is emerald green.
We have Gemini, the twins.
Coming forward, Gemini.
I announce yourselves, your theme is Truth Through Conversation, which is Gemini's Have the Gift of Gab.
I know my dad was the Gemini, he was a great talker, and a good business man, but you know who else was?
Donald Trump, you know, he was born on the 14th, I think, so he's a Gemini.
They're also considered the devils sometimes, just like the Capricorns, because they're kind of like two evil twins.
They're kind of like if the bad seed was the twin.
The other term was evil too. That's how they can be but they lied sometimes
But they don't usually like sometimes it's not for this you depend on which twins one twin the kind of like lies
Fun and one lies only when necessary. Okay
So so Gemini words carry unusual weight today
Listen as carefully as you speak. A chance encounter or unexpected message may reveal a new perspective.
Your message for this gateway is the voice you've been waiting for may be your own. Your color is electric blue.
Next is cancer, the sign we are currently in.
Cancer, your theme is emotional alchemy. So feelings you've tucked away rise to the surface not to overwhelm you but to
Be understood, compassion especially toward yourself becomes a source of strength.
Your message for the gateway is healing begins where honesty meets kindness, and your color
is moon-silver.
Leo, the lion ruled by the sun.
Your theme for this gateway is the true crown
Recognition feels less important than authenticity today
Let your actions speak louder than appearances quiet confidence shines brighter than performance
Leo your message is a real king doesn't need applause and your color is of course gold
Next we have Virgo
Virgo and earthstein
The virgin but they're usually you know
Uh, you know, they're usually not, but okay, but anyway, we made the virgin on the on the uh, I'm a thumbnail too, right?
so
The the theme for this gateway for Virgo is perfect imperfection you don't need
Every answer before taking the next step progress comes through action not flawless planning the space for surprise
your message
perfection is the doorway for guards and
Your power color is a sage green
Libra, I don't know if the thing that is here,
you'll have to rewind to the thing that is.
But your theme is the mirror.
So with this black, wow, a double mirror.
What happens when you put a mirror to a mirror?
I used to figure out when I went to a salon
when I was little, my mom used to do my haircut
at salons occasionally.
And there'd be all the way, yeah,
it looked like I was going through infinity
through these mirrors.
I was like, the salon is a magical place.
It could be like you know going through all these dimensions plus you come out looking completely different, right?
I mean think about these these correlations are amazing, right?
Libra relationships become powerful teachers
Notice what you admire what irritates you and what repeats the mirror isn't judging you. It's inviting understanding
Your message for this gateway is balance begins within and your color is rose quartz
Scorpios, your theme for this black mirror is pretty cool.
It's Phoenix Rising, right?
Something hidden comes to the light,
whether it's a realization, a conversation,
or an inner truth,
facing it directly creates the possibility
for transformation.
Your message, Scorpio, for this black mirror gateway
is every ending carries the seed of a beginning.
And the color for you is black amethyst.
That sounds pretty.
Next we have Sagittarius
Sagittarius is a centaur. The
represent travel. I mean now it's the Sagittarius is the house of travel
I also think of like, you know, Eros like
Shooting an arrow and then Diana also shoots an arrow and she's the moon goes so wow
There's a lot of correlations between everything right Sagittarius
Your theme is the open road.
Adventure may arrive through ideas rather than travel.
Stay curious.
A new philosophy book or conversation
could redirect your path.
Your message is wisdom belongs to the willing traveler.
And your power color is indigo.
Now my sign, my favorite part of the horoscopes,
and it's a Capricorn Aquarius, my sun and moon
and other stuff, but Capricorn.
Building with purpose. You're invited to look beyond achievement and ask whether
your efforts still align with what matters most. A strong foundation is
built with intention as well as discipline and your messages build the
life that reflects your values. And your color is obsidian, the beautiful black
obsidian, shiny black. Aquarius.
Our air sign Aquarius, the water bearer, your theme is future vision, the unconventional idea that you've been considering deserves another look.
Innovation comes from seeing possibilities, others overlook. Share your perspectives with the conference.
Your message is tomorrow begins with today's imagination and your color is neon violet.
Okay, we have one more and then we have a short collective one.
Pisces, finally, Pisces will buy Neptune who rules dreams.
Your theme is appropriately the dream between worlds.
So your intuition is especially vivid today.
Pay attention to dreams, symbols,
and moments that feel meaningful.
Creativity becomes a bridge between the inner
and outer worlds.
Your message is trust, quiet wisdom beneath the surface.
And your power color is ocean blue.
So I want to close with this. This is up for everybody to take in and whatever applied to you with any of those
You know that there's good advice for everybody in there, right?
And we all have different things in different signs and
So the 7-7 gateway invites reflection before action. It encourages releasing patterns that no longer serve
listening to intuition and stepping forward
with greater clarity.
Rather than asking, what should I become?
Today's energy asks, what no longer needs to define me?
So let's all remember this and say it together.
Repeat after me.
I welcome clarity.
Go ahead.
I welcome clarity, okay.
I release when no longer serves me.
I step through the gateway with courage, wisdom,
and open heart.
There we go. We're going through the gateway, right? I mean, I would like it to be like more of like a
Hey, what's up a group ghost of the beta is that ghost? Is that the real ghost you're
Hey, reality Nancy's doing the year. Yeah, why is everyone banned? Everyone's not banned. I don't think so
I mean, I'm gonna go check my a ban list though because I might have had a rogue
Who knows?
have a look see but some people should be banned I mean it's like you know like
there are I do have mods that like look out for me and uh I've instructed them
if they if they see somebody like just like like behind my back talking terrible
shit we can just quietly just okay seven seven is a sacrifice day and so I've
decided it to sacrifice the rudest trolls in the chat but that's all I'll say
Let me use my YouTube studio
And
Like can you guys have a streamer camp or something called streamer camp?
I think it's I think the application process is closed, but what I'm fun to do
it's basically like
You go through like you do streams and something go through the go
You send her some certain famous streamer or something like that and you learn stuff and
Um, I'm just looking at some stuff too right now. Let me see
Tiger. Oh my gosh
Entire group of tricksters are down for the count. I like the idea of that
You know
tricksters like when you think of trickster you know the tricksters they
can be con men too right and what are they what is the common need a common
needs a fool and that you know also if it's interesting as a fool it means
innocence right but it also means it can mean foolish but I like to think of like
the fool more when it's upright the card before the tarot card I think it's
mainly like an innocence that's like a
It's like you don't know what's gonna happen because you've never done before it's a new thing
You're gonna step out. You don't know what you don't know what's gonna happen because it's like it's all new
But if it's upside down that kind of can mean
You're making a foolish step or maybe misstep, but it's just interesting to see how it kind of is
Tied to different things, you know, like everybody plays the fool
Yeah, I've been getting like just like I see like little
Bisions, okay, so this woman's this this guy looks kind of cool. Oh, it was eight days ago
But if I see something that has the right like number of minutes and stuff for the right
I'll get a feeling about it actually. I'm really into numerology and
intuition and
Science, okay, so there's something about it evidence of a plot to harm with death spells. Oh my gosh
Did anybody know people?
People doing death. That's like the worst thing to do is like any kind of magic the best kind of magic is magic
That heals or magic that defends right and that's gonna be stronger because it's like you can come with it from a
Like a stronger place that's for protection
the people that have to
could do the negative magic, they usually need a lot of people to do it, to have any kind of strength,
because it's kind of weak, because it's like hard to sum it up so much negative energy. Well,
maybe not for some people in this community, there's just negative Nellies, but right.
Some people, I mean, there's some negativity here, but I don't know. But I enjoy discovering
How to destroy a witchcraft. It's just weird. You're the matrix. Oh, there's been a lot of matrix kind of
Synchronized there's been
Let's see what else is that well seven seven and I mean the alien did the disclosure kind of stuff
I'm just looking I find like really cool
Okay, so I like this is called be I just like the term the signal so check this out
This is somebody else's work. It's called Drop Ghost, but I would never drop you. No shade.
They cut the wires, called it done, buried my voice beneath the hum
Thought silence could erase my name, but girls don't vanish, we reframe
A static stitch beneath my skin, I learned to scream without it in
Left in ruins, left unseen, but shadows broadcast what they mean
You can't kill, what won't stay gone?
You can't mute, what hums this long?
I found more beneath your doubt, save me
Still screaming, just changing
I'm in broken code, echoed pain where secrets froze
Turned my wounds to frequencies, barcatched from dead machine
You watched me fake hold me insane, tied my name to static blame
But fractured things transmit the best I sing through and I confess
They killed the light, they closed the feed
But I still burn in data streams
You tried to mute me with your lies
But ghosts don't fish ghosts, they'll scream
I'm still breathing
You silenced the signal, but static remembers
Every broken sound becomes a hem. Every muted screen becomes a frequency here.
The ghost becomes lightning.
Here's one more.
I wanna shake this.
Thank you.
When everyone's banned, I'm looking through their things.
Hey, psych.
What was that last song you played I liked that one dog
The band is called drop ghosts
But like I said, I would never drop who's gonna drop me. I wouldn't drop you
But if I did I wouldn't be on your head. I know but you drop me we can run once. Yeah
Okay, yeah, yeah
What's up? How are you?
I miss you. I don't appreciate you didn't I gave you a compliment in the comments by the way
You know, let me look at it. Oh ghost gave me a compliment. He said he said he said he said
um
Stuff cuz you're nice. Oh you said nice glasses. I said I said yeah kind of like a young cyclops
And that has the word psych in it psych. Yeah, exactly. That's you know, hey, mine's gonna like you
But I need to have one. I don't only have one eye though
No, the Cyclops has two eyes like unless you're talking about like the actual Cyclops like
I'm talking about X-Men. Oh
I need to have a few things that like change the meanings of like real real sometimes they have accurate stuff
But yeah, I don't like how it cyclops with two eyes a cyclops has one eye
Then do you see that dumb ass? Why can't call it dumb ass?
But do you see that movie coming out they're making the remake in the Odyssey or whatever it's called?
Yeah, it has a lot of great actors in it, but I'm pretty sure that's gonna be a shit movie
I don't know but I'm pretty sure and that's a very like epic kind of tale and it's like I would say oh, yeah
I mean, three moves, like three or four moves out of it, you know, easily, right?
I mean, they could just take, but then it's like people have to just short
attention span, they went up, I don't know what they're going to put in it,
because there's so much that happens in that book.
Well, everyone was bitching about Elliot Page or whatever her name is.
It was Ellen, whatever, whatever his, her, I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, Elliott now, but they're supposed that's supposed to play Achilles like do you know who Achilles is?
This was gay was the greatest the warrior ever, but he was the greatest worry ever
Ever the gate that you know why they had get great gay warriors is because like when they had gay couples
They like love each other and so they like are really really predictive of each other instead of just like you know
You're strong that's not true at all
Let me let me go ahead and give you a little pushback, and I'm gonna give you too much tonight because I'm chilling tonight, but
This is why we don't let women join the infantry because if they were there, guess what men would do?
You know straight men, they have a hero complex
They'll fucking risk your lives to save the woman more than they would do their own brothers
And that's why we don't let women in the infantry plus they're weaker because they can't let this much
Plus they can't do
I mean that that that was a toxic take and I you know, I don't know who else is listening here, but I think I have to
I think we have an all drag queen or all transgender. It's called it's called a band of brothers not a band of lovers
Yeah, they'll tell you so there's like all the sick seven seven seven. Hey bad boy. How are you? Yeah, so um, yeah
So there's nothing called the sacred band of thieves. Have you heard of the sacred band of thieves?
No, but I'm sure you explain go ahead. Well, hold on one second. I'm gonna bring it
I'm gonna tell you what it was. Okay, so the sacred band of thieves
and okay, so
Uh, so this was whoa, whoa
Actually, I just got a did you just did you make a song and I'm sorry to interrupt you
Did you make a song that you're gonna kick me out? No
No, I go ahead band of band of thieves or whatever you say, okay
So this is the sacred band of thieves was an elite unit of the Theban army
Comprised of 150 gay gay male couples totaling 300 men
They were formed under the leadership of Gorgidas, but first achieved fame under the general
Pelopidas they remain invincible from 378 to 338 BC when the entire troop fell together at the Battle of
Well, because it's like they were smaller. They're not many gay couples. I mean, it sounds like Atlanta. That's a problem
They've been they're pretty good the military unit for service mentioned in 324 BC in this beach against Des Mothinas by the orator
Denocris, okay, so it says the sacred band fell together under a single unit and according to Plutarch were mourned by Philip II of Macedon
And then this is and you know, you know who you know who got them straight men. So why are you bringing this up?
That's like a fucking one-off
They survived for a little bit, but they got
This is what this is what the play though would play to say there's something gay going on here
Okay, so listen this numerous are the witnesses who acknowledge love to be the eldest of the gods
And not only is he the eldest, but he is also the source of the greatest benefits to us
For I know not any other greater blessing to young man who is beginning life than a virtuous lover or lover than a beloved
Oh my gosh, for the principle of what Josh would be kind the men who didn't knowably live at principles
I say now their kindred no honor no wealth or any other motive is able to implant so well as
The world being of honor and dishonor without
which neither states nor individuals could ever do any good or great work.
And I say that the lover who is detected in doing any dishonorable act
or submitting through cowardice, when any dishonor is done to him by another,
be more pained at being detected by his beloved than at being seen by his father
or by companions or by anyone else. The beloved is basically saying that they were
no, no, no, that said nothing about gay shit.
That said something about being loved by your father.
You always want to make your father. That's what that meant.
No, I said the love of them was even greater.
It's a disapproval of your lover would be even greater
than disapproval of your father,
because that's how close you are.
Yeah, you wanna, yeah, that's obvious though.
You wanna be like, because back in the war days,
like you want to honor your father,
you want to have a glorious death,
and you want to honor your brothers.
Nothing about fucking or loving them, you heard?
Like that's more.
Nevermind, I mean, I had to edit it a little bit.
Am I not?
Yeah, I thought you had a good point there, but.
I am entertaining. Thank you. There's three thousand. I do have a good one. I didn't say you weren't entertaining. I've never won so bad.
I totally didn't. I totally didn't. I'm just a RG. Well, thanks for RG's. At least, you know, you said something. You did say something nice last night, but otherwise, I mean, besides, just like, nice.
Well, compare that to how many times he says some root shit. It's like, what, eight to one?
I don't know. And it was, you know, it was in response to something very rude.
Talking about shit.
I mean, I won't discuss it, but I'll just say he said something nice. But then...
He started getting into allegations that I've been I'm on meth and blah blah and I need to be drug tested
And I need to be kicked out of my place. And so and it's like then these kind of take off and so
Yeah, a little burden of proof would be nice on hit on his part. You'd have to prove my buddies
I'm not you'd have to prove that he should be kicked out
You got to prove it all like me because of ran a queue or whatever
I don't know. Well, that's all news. No one even did
You give these people like a couple weeks they move on
He's banned. I mean Brandon is banned. I mean he's never coming again. He said I he was trying to like
Like pretend to be a 12 year old girl and then get modded. So he didn't wait. Yo
Yeah, don't I don't I don't know about it. I don't care about it. He's trying to do
He's like he's like, oh, I caught you. I sent a 12 year old girl to like become your mod
And I was like, why are you talking to a 12 year old girl? And then he's in the left
I mean, that's a good point. Why are you talking to a 12 year old girl though?
like that's a good point you got him. I got him yeah I usually do because it's like I mean I I'm
that's a good thing about it like you know we'll just use their own logic against them
instead of feeding them to it let's use their own logic right
Yeah, and it's kind of like winning the game, right? So but how have you been lately?
You know, I mean, you know, I know you've been going through some I've some bullying to online and stuff
And well, I wouldn't necessarily call it bullying. I just got tired of it. It's not really boy
You can't really bully me because I don't really
Every day say the same shit every night for the past like it's like how many times I got to win this shit
Like I'm getting tired of talking about it. Well, yeah
And it's like maybe because you have talked about it
But you know maybe you just like just ignore them and not even like address it and just say I've been doing that
Have you not been listening I've been doing that well
I can't listen to what's not being said I mean it's like but I've been I've been
seeing you on panel like lately but have you seen me on any panels like I got my speed
a little bit yeah we were in the panel the other night uh and it was actually you which I didn't
by the way my bad I didn't actually know it was you you thought I was an imposter yeah
because I fucking caught the texture you didn't answer or nothing but then you were there and I
was like that's his voice and then I was like all right and I just went to bed I should be on
Hey, look at this what
Fuck is that Justin Timberlake? Yeah, I'm getting my bed
My bed looks like a phone. It looks like Justin Timberlake. Oh, thank you
Justin Timberlake thing going on or something like a young JT
a young Justin Timberlake, well, that's a compliment.
Tell me you love me.
I mean, you can go Justin Timberlake or Jive Turkey.
Whichever one you want to pick.
This is scary.
Why does the anthropic have that as the, I mean, gosh,
that seems like, what if there will be
Illuminati or something?
Geez, Claude, I mean, come on.
Elon Musk, Joseph Holds, Elon Musk's fraud verdict.
I appreciate you for asking me how I've been doing though,
because no one ever asked me that,
and I appreciate you for asking.
Yeah, I've been out for a while, but I'm back now and I'm I might have to crash it
I might have to crash a panel tonight. You know, okay
Well, I mean, I saw somebody I was on a new panel named blaze on this guy. Have you been to blazes yet? Oh
No, but Chris I don't know. Yeah, his name is blaze something. I feel like blazes something
I know I wasn't even subscribed, but I went and like cuz summer was there like, you know yelling at yelling at Amanda
It was great. She was like you don't that bitch and it was so funny. I love nice. Yeah, it was great
So, hey, goes this picture of you. Oh, let me see
I need to turn off my background. I'm so sorry. Everyone told you about the
I know I let him in but so did good time. So did you know clumsy is like what and I let him
I let him make a fool of himself RG and so what?
And what like everyone told you about that dude and let him anyway dude you can't even make the argument though
Just because you're told something he has to he asked us to figure it out himself
Like because you say it like we don't trust you RG. I don't even try to say why do
I didn't trust him and he's like hey, don't let her up on your panel. Let's assume. I had a panel
Let her up until she did something then I'd make my own thing
I'm not gonna trust anybody so this because you want somebody on your panel don't let them fucking hate on you
Oh, we told you this but you guys talk RG everyone talks a lot of shit about everyone
They'll make up anything so don't fucking believe that yeah
We made up her own mind dog and you said he's gone now that looks like me by the way
Just pointing that out
Yeah
I don't know what the argument is like you we're not gonna fucking just believe Brandon people on the internet
Even if you joined the panel before even if you like you when I just gonna fucking fully believe
RG you're right. Alexander's last night be nice to her and stuff like on our panel
Even more than I was I like I like if you got mad at me because I stopped supporting
Explain yourself RG come up here
Yeah, he was he was all in and you know who told me the evidence against Brandon was Tony the Tony the conductor
Like why would I listen to him about anything? I mean, it's like really he's the person that it was harassing me and stuff
Well, I think someone that told me that and then she crashed on me about it
And I was I don't know anything about it
Then I talked to you about it and then you know, that's what I heard of it
He says that like I said three soon to be two. What does that mean?
How are you gonna hate it on somebody like you have somebody on the just because you don't like them doesn't mean they shouldn't be up there
Let us assume you're fucking on a live or we don't know that shit
Here's the thing though psyche like we brought you facts that literally no facts at all they didn't bring
No, it's like and it's so confusing. They just accuse someone of something. I was like, well let that man defend himself and let him tell it.
It wasn't even a crime. I mean, it was like, you know, it was like, there's a crime, then it's prosecutable, right?
There's like, there's no prosecution. There's like, you know, she was down there in, um, in New Mexico.
I don't know enough about it and I just want to stay out of it.
I'll just stay out of it, but she was down in Mexico saying that she was, she got in his like, you know, this, you know, illegal immigrant prostitute or whatever.
They didn't speak English. They couldn't testify. I mean, it's just a crazy story. But anyway, we'll leave it alone.
He's been threatening me and stuff.
And they're doing the same thing, Brandon.
And then she actually went on a big attack on him too.
Why is he threatening you?
Cause you kicked him off your panel?
Yeah.
No, I'm gonna tell him to suck a dick from the back and make sure it's of age
He kept saying I have AIDS he called me stupid
Call me an idiot and then and it's like and he talked down to me and he said oh
I mean he should have said that's a funny joke
He should have said you have like maybe maybe your method that it might been funnier
That's what everyone is saying right like it's like to and it's like just annoying them. Oh, well, you know, someone call his
I'm calling to say that he's on on drugs and you know kicking him out of his apartment and so I mean
It's like what is it? Get a life worry about your own life. Well, it's like all you gotta do is hit him with a little burden of proof
Okay, you made the they made the claim go ahead and prove it. You made the claim
Offered the whole the whole I went to the whole episode. There's no evidence for anything offered is
By the way, I was in your chat last night. Oh you are
Yeah, you're hiding for me. No, you're playing songs. Oh my god. How loud is that train? I
Mean, that's a ghost thing like right outside your house that the train the tracks is it go like right?
It sounds like it's right going by your window with those. It's literally right there like it's literally right here
Cuz it's a crossroads brother, I've lived right here. It's a process. It's a lot of home
I'm so sorry. I mean, that's that must be nightmare. How is it all through the night? It does that
Here's the thing though. I've lived here for like 20 something years and uh, I'm just used to it
You're used to it
It's like it's like one of those smoke alarm batteries. Like, you know, you know, I'm not black
Sorry
I apologize for that. That was that was that was offensive my bad. I didn't mean to do that. Yeah
Okay, so it goes
What about watermelon?
Oh my god
Hey, you should get like a you should get like a truck
That is you seem like here's the thing that isn't seem love to me that is very loud
Doesn't seem love to me though. I'm used to it dog. I know but it's like me
Do you know that that's why we probably can't listen to anybody else?
You probably are deaf now. I mean you probably like just like
I became a little deaf, but I you know, I love you. You're my friend
No, I'm not mean to you. I'm nice to you. Hey, good. You know, my little watermelon. You're the aliens have come to visit here
That looks like Mary that doesn't look like an alien
Actually, I see a diet of representation Diana, but hold on a second. I mean, is that baby black?
No, oh
shit
To the alien with a halo
Is that cocaine on the table? Yeah
Your table okay, there we go
Your cable be messed I prefer coke brother that picture me goes make you like that pretty accurate. I like it. Yeah
Better than the Michelin man, that's me
I was in the Michelin man. That was a man. No, I said it's better than the Michelin man
Have you ever seen the Michelin man? Yeah, it looks like a man though in the in the safe health marshmallow. Oh, yeah, don't since you
I'm sorry. I'm sorry man. I see man. I hate seeing but I was on your panel
I've been off panels, you know, I come up there like suddenly but I was on your panel last night
And I was listening you're playing you wouldn't even play music though. You're playing like some like new shit or whatever
I think you made I don't even know what happened. I don't even know what it was the thing that is song or I was playing
No, it wasn't a song
Was that video? Yeah, it was a video. Okay, it wasn't a I video either what was but it was like a new I don't even know
I don't fucking know
Did I did a cool video at the Illuminati? Do you see that? I was gonna join then I was like dude
I'm just gonna go to bed. I don't feel like
There's any time I join brother. I'm surprised. There's not people here right now. They want there's well, is there somebody that wants to run it?
I'm not
My rings tonight goes
Oh, is that the green ring, the pink ring, the yellow ring, and the red ring, so if you,
so green ring means fall, yellow mean rings angry, I mean hatred, and then the red ring
means angry, and then the pink ring means love, so if you can go like, have you ever
seen, have you ever seen a pink ring, or a pink ring, or a green ring, there's a black
ring.
No, is that, are you doing like some DC shit, like, you know, Green Lantern shit?
Yeah, they're like their magical jewel. Yeah. Well, there's a couple of cool symbols
But this is yellow sapphire right there and then there's this one
We can make it all up
But if you punch a person in the face with that might fuck them up. I'll be honest with you
You could you could try
Hey listen, you could try it
No, you could try it though. I'd knock you to fuck out though. Okay, I would just hire something
I would just hire like Mike Tyson. Why would you want to run one with me?
I want to wrestle with you, but not not just punch you in the face.
I mean...
Boy, you asked me if you could punch me in the face, and I said yes, sir.
You can.
Would you like that?
I mean...
Yeah, you could try it.
I'd like it too if you tried to punch me in the face.
I'd love it.
Wow.
Ghost like is rough play.
I'ma knock you to fuck out, and when you wake up and back, did you like it?
And you're like, yeah, I like it.
Just don't pee in the bed, please. No, I know and you know you stop that gay shit, bro
I've been telling you that stop that get shit with me. You can talk to anyone else but me, dog
Also, you try to tussle that's a gay
I didn't say that for it. You said you said the phrase gay effort. I did not say that
Okay, I thought you did missing this hurt. Are you not do you want to find the words that are coming out of my mouth?
Neo
Would you say? I'm sorry. I called you Neo. You look like the one them
Well, that's what's like, you know like I you know Alan started making these like really offensive like drawings
They're nice of everyone else, but they're really bad of bad of me. I mean, it's like and then it's like
The thing is it's like even Brandon looks good and then he's like, oh, I look like he's Brandon things that he looks like the
You know Neo from them or the Matrix and like, you know, I annexed this great in it and then there's well
It's good. And then I'm like that like all they can make an argument to myself. That's not a good argument
I said it like you look like Neo. No if you had black shades on then you'd look like Neo. I'm not red shades
You look like daredevil
But then you just look like a dumb dumb. Yeah, you look like they're dumb
Not fucking neo not anything else. That's red shades only person that wears red shades. I know is dare double
So do you know what the seventh letter of the alphabet is?
ABCD it's fuck you I think F you know, it's G
The seventh letter is G
FG it's was G. So, you know what a G is what it looks like. I'm a real motherfucking G
What number does the G look like?
It looks like Pac-Man eatin shit. You just making sure that no, no, I'm looking number six. Okay, so it's like 66
so
So it might have been a gateway to hell who knows what that with the latest well that would you'd have their third six on there
Maybe
Well, but there might have been what they're okay. Well, I know it come on now to the 2026
Yeah, there is every time I join your panel. Do I think I have a I think I have a cross-up to join your panel
It's seven seven six, which is G G six, which is 66. There you go. Well, you're a numerology to
Yeah, and I'm alright. Bye. Bye. Well, that was interesting
Okay, but anyway, Ghost wasn't really listening when I was reading that article.
I'll just read one more paragraph.
It says, the kind of same-sex relationship, both Plato and Crompton, are referencing as
the Greek model of male love in which a lover, the Aristides, nurtured the growth and cultivation
of the beloved, the erenimos, a younger man.
The paradigm is considered an important aspect of the agage.
Um, and there's GG, you know, seven seven, uh, the Spartan education program, which
is also produced great warriors.
Okay.
So anyway, it gets more, it gets a little bit more graphic than that, but I'm not going
to, I'm not going to, I was just, just trust me, they were fucking, okay, but, but there
were, but there were the best, there were those, there was just a very small unit though.
You can tarot, not numerology.
Well, I mean all I was doing was like, you know kind of teaching you a little bit
Let me let me I'm gonna show you how to how I work gematria. Hold on
So there's a website called gematria or gematrix, right?
It's called jama- speaking of the matrix where there's gematrix, okay, and all you have to do is go to the site gematrix
And I'm gonna go to gematrix and I'm gonna type Tyler ghosts and we're gonna see what numbers come up
Okay, so like a Tyler ghost
I'll go CrucibleGhost because that's his name, Crucible, C-R-U-C-I-B-L-E-G-H-O-S-T.
So if I go CrucibleGhost, okay, so look at 577, oh my god, it's both 5GG, right, okay.
So it says, so what does it correspond to?
In Hebrew, he made a lie, his bride died.
It says six million. It says, uh, oh, do you see it on the screen? No, you can't see it on the screen. I'm sorry
There you go. It says
Countries it says bullet train ghost the train is by you it says bullet train and that's but your name, right?
Crucible ghost says I Christ being the air is this famous people. It says melancholy. It says origami
It's October 18th, March 13th, October 18th, okay?
South America, I mean, also motherfucker.
Renunciation, Brussels is facing as big a spear.
I am energy, gestures, dysfunction, dynamics.
Listen to me, Teehee, imaginary, kick a ball,
liar's all going to hell.
And noonie ass fat and rapturing, isn't that interesting?
And then there's different, you know, different systems with different words and stuff, but that was crucible ghosts. And so I just give you a big lesson in numerology.
Time is...
So I guess if you have Claude the upgraded Claude and you can use something called fable right now. It is the most powerful AI
LLM it's even a step above an LLM. I think it's like really fast, but it just burns credits so quick and
We're giving it to people that use Claude code or Claude a
Upgrader for like another week or whatever
so anyway
Numerology is tarot here because each tarot card has a number and you know, I don't need to get into all of it
See what I have though
Dripping from your teeth, say you're holy in the light, but you're drowning underneath
Every word you twist and hide, every truth you bury deep
Yeah, I see it in your eyes, all the secrets that you keep
You smile like a saint, but you move like a thief
Dressing up your dirt in design, I believe
Say it sweet, say it slow, make a moment
Secrets gotta pulse, and they're crawling, don't you sleep
Flicks to confessions in a crack glass frame Say you never did wrong, but you whisper my name
Rewrite history, make yourself go With the truths and the cracks with the story, don't hold you
Tailor every memory, stitch it up tight Turn your demons into angels when you step in the light
Every sing, gotta flip to every scar, get erased But the shadows still remember every lie you replaced
Yeah, polished up the mask real clean But the mirror don't blink, wanna see in what it seems
You built a throne out of fiction and flame Now you're lost in the echo of your own made name
But you're drowning under your words, you twist and hide every truth, you bury deep
Yeah, I see it in your eyes, all the secrets that you keep
You talkin' simple, but it tastes like russet, trust me now, but you choke on trust
If you promise you may gotta crack in the spine, every truth you avoid, just a matter of time
You sculpt your image like a puzzle in space, but it fractures in silence when no one's in place
Every lie like a thread, now you tangled inside, got a web of illusions and no way to hide
Say it again, say it better, make it sound like you were never the villain
If the juice came out, would you recognize the ghost in your reflection behind your own eyes?
You built your kingdom on a fragile disguise. Now it's cracking
You paint your halo
We're very deep. Now your secrets got a voice in the screen and then you sleep. You smile
I ain't put the mask on the bleed and now it's starting, but it's on. They never leave
It was really cool. This is interesting. Hold on.
Whether it's ready or not, but I just want to issue, here we go.
The second part of our study of free of this
have to get this recorded because I just want to get it off my desk
and learn about it. Whether it's ready or not,
but I just want to issue a warning here. Some of this material might be
offensive to some. It's going to get a little graphic.
So we're going to start out with the treatment of Priyapus and Lotus in Avid's Metamorphosis.
Avid mentions Priyapus and Lotus in the Metamorphosis.
Lotus is a nymph who got drunk and passed out at the Liberalia Festival.
Priyapus tried to rape her when everyone was asleep.
causing him to lose his erection, and alerting everyone, including Lotus, to his shenanigans.
He either runs away, or she is changed into a lotus tree.
Priyapas trying to rape Lotus.
This is a painting called The Feast of the Gods by Giovanni Pellini.
Here's and his dome key.
Let's get a detail here.
Here's Priyapus sneaking up on Lotus, Raper, here he is with his Hultent, with his Malintents,
with Sardinus, Donki. He's a very interesting character. I think we'll have a look at him next.
Here's Lotus being changed into the tree. Talk about rape culture. And this is the blue Lotus butterfly.
It's like Tiffany in blue.
The intended rape victim was the goddess Vesta, the Vestal Virgin's fame.
I think they were transgender.
This is a painting called Haiman Ayos disguised as a woman during an offering to Priyapus by Nicola Poussin.
Here's detail, two fingers on the generative principle.
Look at that.
Priyapus.
As a son of Dionysus and Aphrodite, he was in erote, one of the erotes, which makes him sibling to hermaphroditus, eros, and Priapus.
This god is an extremely androgynous god. Looks like a woman to me.
Here's another portrayal of Hyman by Edward Byrne Jones. Extremely effeminate.
Hyman is also the membrane that surrounds the external vaginal opening or the virgin's cherry.
This is a book by Richard Payne Knight, a discourse on the worship of Priapus,
and Richard Payne Knight is a classical scholar, connoisseur, archaeologist, best known for his
He was a member of the Society of Dillatante, widely considered to be an arbiter of taste.
The Society of Dillatante are a very interesting group.
They were established in 1732 as a dining club, made up by a group of men who had been on the
Grand Tour of Europe, led by Sir Francis Dashwood of the Hellfire Club fame.
They are closely associated with Brooks's, one of London's most exclusive gentlemen's
club.
The society quickly became wealthy through a system on which members made contributions
to various funds to support building schemes and archaeological expeditions.
It was a prime mover in the establishment of the Royal Academy.
It's member Richard Chandler was sponsored to go and discover the ancient archaeological site of
Olympia home of the first Olympic games
So I believe this society is very instrumental in
creating
What we know to be ancient history hear that
Society of Noblemen and Scholars which sponsors the study of ancient Greek and Roman art and the creation of new works in the style.
Oh, new works in the style.
This is his Richard Paine Knight's first book, The Worship of Priapus, and he sought to recover the importance of ancient phallic cults.
His penchant for ancient sacred eroticism brought accusations of being an apologist for libertinism.
There's that God-Lieber again. The central claim of the Boucher National that just impulsed
to worship the generative full was articulated through the genital imagery and that this
imagery has persisted into the modern age. He argued that pagan ideas persisted in the
Christian culture. But maybe they're made up and more recent. Fashionists? Oh my god. More imagery of
Priapaea, which is a collection of 95 poems devoted to Priapas, they were humorously obscene.
They were said to be compiled from literary works and Latin literature.
Authorities regard the verses to have been written by a group of poets who met at Mycenae's
house, who was a patron of Horus, amusing themselves by writing tongue-in-cheek tributes
I believe it was more likely written by a group like the Society of Dila Tante.
Right.
Illustrations from the Priyapaea.
The statues of Priyapis were hung with signs bearing epigrams, which graphically threatened
such sexual assault towards transgressors of the garden or anyone who would steal the fruits of
the garden. An epigram is a short satirical poem.
often witty. The Roman epigrams were more obscene than the Greeks.
Another illustration from the Priapaea. There's a couple examples of the epigrams.
Whosoever steals a rosebud or obsconds with herb or apple,
hateful to both boys and women, let him burst from such stiffness.
I warn you boy you will be screwed, girl you will be laid with a third penalty awaits the bearded thief, if a woman steals from me or a man or a boy, let the first give me her cunt, the second his head, the third his buttocks, my dick will go through the middle of boys and middle of girls, but with bearded men it will aim only for the top.
in the Priyapaea. And we'll have a look at a few of them. It's been quite an education.
The first one we'll look at is bestiality. This is the, um, this is pacif, pacifae.
It's about Priyapis. It's a, it's a, you know, watch the whole thing. It's really good.
And it's where the 3,000 daughters, since Oceanus, and, and that makes her a sister to Seercy.
The witch.
The goddess of sorcery.
was the wife of King Minos of Crete.
After ascending the throne over his brothers,
he prayed to Poseidon for a sign of his support.
Poseidon sent a beautiful white bull
to be sacrificed as a symbol of respect for the Olympians.
Minos sacrificed a regular bull instead.
Poseidon sought revenge by having Aphrodite curse Pasiphae
with lust for the bull.
So Pasiphae had
Daudalus, the court artificer, and father of Icarus, make her a wooden cow with cow-hide
covering for her to hide in to receive the amorous bull.
Wow.
Daudalus and Pasiphae by Giulio Romano, 1530.
And this is the artificial cow that Pasiphae is going to disguise herself in.
Another picture of Daudalus creating the artificial cow.
works of this fissuality. This is a surrealist painting by André Masson. This is a sculpture
on a beach in Barcelona by Oscar Estruga. The union of the white bull and pacifist resulted in
Later, Daudalus was asked to build the labyrinth to contain the Minotaur.
This is another subject covered in the Priyapaia.
It's a new word for me, Iromatio.
And you can read yourself about the fine distinction between Iromatio and Felatio.
Basically, it's a form of oral rape.
Another subject covered was infibulation.
this is male infibulation as opposed to the female infibulation where the labia are sewn together
oh my god
but the male infibulation is the placing of a clasp through the male foreskin in ancient Greece
male athletes singers public performers used a clasp to close the foreskin and draw the penis
over to one side in a practice known as kind of does name literally meaning dog time
In Rome, a fibula or ring was used. It was a sign of restraint, abstinence, modesty.
I crossed this practice when I was looking at the ancient Olympic athletes who were supposed to practice this kind of disney.
The Priyapaia was later translated into English by Leonard C. Smithers and Sir Richard...
Sir Richard Burton is a very interesting character.
Nickely Moethe and Dick.
He was a British explorer, geographer, translator, soldier,
writer, orientalist, cartographer, spy, linguist, poet,
fencer, and diplomat.
He was famed for his travels and extraordinary knowledge
of languages and cultures.
He was said to have spoken 29 different languages, many,
many.
photographs of this character, if he was a real character or not.
It's a huge mustachio.
That looks like a man right there with me.
That looks like a man.
He also translated A Thousand and One Arabian Nights
and the Kamasutra and the Arabic sex manual,
the Perfumed Garden.
He was knighted in 1886.
This is the tomb.
I'm watching something.
The mausoleum.
Actra.
Let's say crucified.
feminist Priyapus, an in-depth study of Roman sexual satire, and a commentary on the effects of all humor on society and its victims.
Remo Priyapus, these are some final images of Priyapus in his fertility god tutorial.
The garden gnome is said to be a leftover of this regarded Priyapus.
There is a church in Montreal
Dedicated to Priyapus
The St. Priyapus Church
Founded in the 80s by D.F. Cassidy
The following is mainly homosexual men in Canada and the United States semen is also treated with reverence and its consumption in an act of worship
Seaman is esteemed as sacred because of its divine life-giving power
Cassidy sexuality seems to be in question. There is also a Priapus shot that you can get for
erectile dysfunction. The key shot involves harvesting your own plasma and rich growth
factors in your blood, injecting them into the specific areas of the penis. The process involves
drawing a small amount of blood into a centrifuge where it spins for about 10 minutes to separate
It's re-injected into ostensibly, stings the blood flow and the penis appear larger and rejuvenated.
It's also an o-shot for women. This is the Priyapus butterfly.
So that is it for Priyapus. I would love to hear your thoughts in the comments section.
How is that?
Thank you very much for watching.
I can. It's pretty good.
Okay.
The raunchiest guard from Greek and Roman mythology.
Yeah, yeah, so pretty interesting. I love mythology and I
Remember I came across that in the sacred text book and I was like whoa
That's um and I was like these are kind of like raunchy
There's actually some like Roman stuff, too
That is like very raunchy. I was like this doesn't seem like it's like as I didn't like they just invent the the printing press in like
1500 something and like Germany like how do they have all these old texts from like, you know, Greece
Then I started looking at the numbers. I mean, it's I it's I've covered some exciting stuff
but I'll hold I'll hold off on saying too much about it though, but
There is somebody that I used to watch on YouTube and he's very
Genuine he's very sweet. He's like yeah, and his name is Franchot blue
He's very he's almost like a profit energy kind of thing, but he also picked up on a lot of things that I was
Picking up and sometimes we have the same thing sometimes we have the we have different views of things, but
He's some pretty fun. He has some interesting stuff. I'm just gonna see if there's something that maybe
We can have a look at
It's a
Yeah, so okay, so do you hear what those people that climb the Empire State Building? Okay. I didn't I?
I heard that I was like, well, what does that mean?
That sounds like, you know,
doing King Kong, climbing the Empire State Building.
I mean, who would climb it?
Like, if two people climbed it, how?
Like, the rock climbing?
There's, he goes over, I think.
I haven't seen this, but let's give it a chance.
And see if you'd like, Franchot, Peters, Pearson.
There's a couple that climbed the Empire State Building.
Yes, she heard me.
The Empire State Building in New York.
Of course, New York.
Folks over there crazy.
Not all of them, but some folks they're crazy what a cute and then as they climb back down
The guy got on one knee and he proposed
I'm like, what is that about?
seem kind of strange
Did the same time?
Trump was over in I think it was Dakota and he gave a speech and he mentioned Kamala Harris
Well Pearson, what does one have to do with the other?
Because I'm noticing
that many times in the last six months,
Matthew 24, where it speaks of the birth pains,
you know, with birth pains and you have contractions,
that means you have, it's a sign that something's coming
because the contractions are happening more and more
in a short period of time.
I know I'm all over the place.
What I'm trying to say is that
Trump mentioned Kamala Harris today,
this wedding, this engagement, yeah, that's more accurate,
this engagement on the Empire State Building roof
by this guy, it spoke to Kamala Harris.
I know, I know, I know, it's confusing,
but wait till you see it.
It's July 1st, 2026, 735 and the PM, happy Wednesday,
and praise God for whom all bless this flow.
Check it out.
We had a beautiful day in November 5th and we went in by a lot, we went by just a lot,
it was incredible.
We beat a woman named Kamala.
We beat a brilliant young woman named Kamala who had no clue.
She was the border czar.
She never went to the border.
She never called the border patrol.
I said, fellas, do you ever get a call from Kamala?
She's the border czar.
No sir, she never called.
I used to call them every other day.
Why this couple was climbing the Empire State Building and here's the story and there they are at the top check it out
Two people have climbed all the way up there on the antenna spider
And you see them and they're holding a banner and what that banner says is when the power of love beats the world of power, the world knows peace.
Oh my God.
They are in New York.
How many blocks down there?
It's really just a huge amount of work.
It's over 30, 30 tenths.
That's basically, you know, between 30 and 30.
So can you believe that?
I'm going to read this to you.
Two Empire State Building climbers in custody
after apparently getting engaged at the top.
Okay, two people climbed to the very top
of New York City's Empire State Building,
unfurled a banner,
and then apparently got engaged Wednesday afternoon.
The two have since been arrested.
They put their names out there and everything.
Then they say they faced a host of
charges, you think, battery, and reckless,
not burglary, reckless endangerment, criminal mischief,
violation of local law, da, da, da, da, da, decline.
It was a wedding proposal that gripped the city.
It started at around noon Wednesday when a man and a woman who could be seen wearing masks
reached the very top of the Empire State Building and unfurled a large black banner with white
lettering.
There was no visible safety equipment and clung to their fingerprints, right, whatever.
When the power of love beats the love of power, the world knows peace.
The quote is often attributed to Jimi Hendrix.
Now, preliminary information indicates
the two got in through a hatch on 103rd floor
used for water, tower, maintenance,
lake enforcement sources told CBS News.
Now, notice the words,
used for water, tower, maintenance, water.
A woman's water bag breaks.
Am I right?
Okay, just follow me, follow me.
Because just so you guys know, new subscribers,
Kamala means lotus flower.
I did not know that I've been lotus.
It's a lotus flower analogy.
She gives birth.
So there's gonna be a water break of some kind
and or Kamala's coming back to be president,
but just I'm getting ahead of myself.
Let me break this thing down here. We can listen to the people
as we talk about. By the way, a lot is going on in this area over the next few days. I mean this is
where we think Travis Kelsey and Taylor Swift are getting buried in Mass Square Garden. I'm not
trying to make a joke. I'm just trying to tell you it's in the very same neighborhood that a ton
is going on. It's a short distance from here. The F.R. Staple is 102 stories. I think with
the spire it's 103. I'm trying to look to see if they even have any kind of harness or anything of
It doesn't. It does not look like it. Uh, as somebody who has severe anxiety, bad
heights, it's like, honestly, even hard for me to imagine this. Uh, and as you said,
it's important not to make a joke. I mean, obviously these are protesters. They're trying
to make a point. They're trying to get seen. They are. Uh, this is quite a dramatic way to do it.
Why? And they were on social media, on social media, believe it or not. Now let's go forward.
When the power of love beats the love of power
The world knows peace
Empire State Building July 1st, 2026. I put that in Jomartia Calculator
Right across the way. Oh
Look what it comes out to
11 it comes out to 9 11
If there is a water break cycle a psychologically or spiritually or some kind remember
the Twin Towers are in New York.
So when I put that line that they had on that banner,
an empire state building and the date, I get 9-11.
Okay, I'm sure you can read that by now.
It's right there.
Now check this out.
You see because there's no way in the world
you're supposed to make that breach.
I did security for 19 years.
I don't care what they say, it's garbage.
they weren't supposed to get there, okay? So this was all set up by the powers. Now,
9-Eleven 2001, you know what happened Twin Towers? Today is July 1st, 2026. The difference is 24
to 24th letter of the alphabet is X. X means I'm taking you out and 293. What is 293?
The 293rd day of the year, which is right there, is October 20th.
And what's the October 20th?
Kamala Harris, her birthday right there is October 20th.
Yeah, it's Libra.
Are you with me?
I'm with you.
Now, you take her birthday, October 20th, 1964,
from July 1st, 2026, you get she's 61 years old today,
and what is 814?
Japan surrendered to America on 814.
That's right, 814.
And it was an unconditional surrender.
Isn't that what Trump been asking of Iran?
Okay.
Now, it's also, not only 814, it's also 254.
What is 254?
Four plus two.
Five.
The 254th day of the year, my friend, is 9-11.
Oh my God.
The 254th day of the year is 9-11.
Brilliant, huh?
There's a place you can interpret stuff.
I might say prayers of the Lord.
Oh, that's interesting.
Now, and I ain't so mob me, brilliant, but you know, hey.
Now, this reminded me of the clown
who climbed the bridge in Washington, D.C. May 1st.
Remember I did a video on it.
Okay.
Look at this. This guy climbed a Frederick Douglass bridge a few months ago. Look I
Believe he was protesting the war now as he was up there. I had noticed that
It might not have it here
but
When he was up there
Let me see if I can
Show other pictures
When he was up there
Here it is here
See that there written see that there. It's not a banner. It's like a long
fabric or something
Now I believe that is the lotus flower, but hold tight. Let me show you a connection right quick
The Frederick Douglass bridge of which he climbed it was founded. It was completed on 9 11
Oh my 9 11 2021. You probably barely see that. Of course. That's me. One of the eyes.
9 11. I know right. Okay. Now watch this. Let me go back. I want you to show I want to show you
what it's about. If the client want to go up here and chill out, let him go up there. If he fall down,
let him fall. Let him fall. Look, we got three wheels, don't we? Okay, well, let him do what he
But another stage you've been.
Well, Pearson, what you used to, look, people, look.
I don't think, I think we got better things to do
than sit here and watch this dude and call it a bridge.
But I'm gonna tell you what it's about.
But once you see the bridge,
you're gonna realize it's everything
I've been telling you about.
Hello?
That's familiar?
What I've been telling y'all for the last two weeks.
Huh?
That's what it's about.
A archway, a tunnel, or a gateway?
OK.
Let me show you how to tunnel.
Let's look at this tool, this one's real, right?
Let's look at this.
Come on, man.
Quick and easy.
So it's like an arc. The bridge is like an arc, right? And I showed all the all the different
arcs that I've been showing. Here it is here.
It's our art, they're playing baby, they're playing, they're playing, they're playing.
Because you follow this channel, you know what's up, in Washington D.C. on July 4th, they're
putting up a 250 foot arch and in celebration of our 250th anniversary, okay?
Two plus five.
Now, I've been telling people, welcome new subscribers, you in the right spot because
I don't think nobody else has, uh, explained this thing to other people.
If they are God bless them.
But I'm sure I'm over the first one to break the story.
And I can't go to, and I can't go to, there's the devil.
He comes to an arch, a gateway, a tunnel.
They go into a new world order.
You understand?
The purple rain, the R-E-I-G-N.
That's the R-A-I-N.
No, no, no.
You see this here?
This lady, God bless her, April 5th, Jenae Robinson, she was in what, Africa, and they say she
underlined herself, which I don't believe, she's under a drag, that's the arts way, you
know what I'm saying?
And I'm sure everybody heard about this one, for 84-year-old Nancy Guthrie, been missing
since February 1st, this guy came and got her, they say, she reached for the red can.
or do you know about something like the archway that he's up under?
He's under the archway. So they create these events to tell you
and I wouldn't be surprised within the next couple of weeks or the next 48 hours they find her
or try to solve this. Now let's go to this connection. Remember I told you when you look at that
when you look at that what is this fabric that's coming down when he's on top of a bridge
You coming to something new remember I told you you got a birth coming on a birth
Well, you know you got
They like a biblical court, right?
Have to beat me up the cord is connected between the baby and the mother. I stutter so that's that's what it is
I know what it is. So don't put it in the chat. I just
stutter that way but
That's like the cord that connects the baby to the mother. Okay now. How do I how do I see that?
Kamala means lotus flower.
The lotus flower is symbolic in Egyptian history.
The lotus flower gives birth to a god that's coming.
That's why I say the birth pains, the contractions,
there are more.
Watch this, you'll put it together for you.
This what you see is like the tale of the lotus flower.
To me, that's what it means.
Watch this.
It's commonly accepted that the Lotus is the symbol of resurrection and rebirth of a new life, of eternal lives.
There are aquatic plants that is to send out their roots deep into the dark fertile mud below them.
You see the stems? You see the stems? That's what this is. That's the stems. I believe that's what this is.
We're going to put it all together with the marriage.
It's an arch.
Arch is the birth way, yeah.
Waterline.
Then their stem and bud reach upward toward the surface
until it breaks forth into the daylight.
They just kind of happily float on the water,
soak up the sun, following its light
throughout the course of the day.
And it closes its bud at night and sinks back down
beneath the water.
to do it all over again the next day.
You're just gonna say like Rob, the sun guy, like Rob.
Resurrection.
Rob.
Like Rob emerging from the cosmic ocean.
And you may remember from our first lessons
that Rob is often shown actually coming forth.
Out of the lotus flower, there's Rob in Egyptian history.
There's the snake that the Egyptians wore on the head
and there's the falcon.
But this is Kamala, the lotus flower, birthing this antichrist that's coming.
They're killing a new system that's coming. That's why it's an arch. It's symbolic.
It's an archway. Something's going to come through it. I know you're getting it now.
I know you're getting it now.
From the opening petals of the lotus blossom.
What is?
Of the lotus blossom. Now look.
What day did this guy climb?
He climbed, he climbed that arch, that bridge,
that Frederick Douglass Bridge, May 1st, 2026.
Check that date, May 1st, 2026.
Today is July 1st, 2026.
The difference is eight six, eight six.
Don't think if you watched the last video and the ones the last two three days, you know, you know exactly what 86 is
You know exactly what 86 is. Let me introduce you guys
last video
I'll bring it to you in a second out of the commercial 86 you see how God work you moving
All right, this is your age six or I have that was a year ago and 514
514 is his birthday. Oh, come on man. Come on man. And like I told y'all
Judy sitting with betrayed from within
Somebody close to it. It's coming now and I've said this before too
Lee Harvey Oswald would come back into the picture at the end.
Lee Harvey Oswald, to me, was the patsy.
I don't believe he took out a JFK,
but his birthday was so significant.
Lee Harvey Oswald, the one who they said took out a JFK.
His birthday is October 18th, 1939.
To the 18th, like Luke to the 18th,
Jesus told his disciples,
I saw Satan as lightly being hurled out of heaven,
Luke 10 18 and remember the horses bolted
The horses bolted they said bolted
Bolted that's like lightning. You understand the condition lightning a strike a lightning strike. So let's look at it
Let's look let's let's look at this thing
If we heard the Oswald birthday is 10 18
1939 right here. We have our own birthday the last people come
is July 10, 2026, Trump will be there.
The difference is 86 years ago
when Lee Harvey Oswell was born and 274.
What is 274?
I just showed you, 274, you should be screaming by now.
274 is the God's soul in victims.
And he gotta eat, it's called sacrifice.
Aurelion brought in the new religious system.
The Sun God, soul and victors.
That's 274.
And then there's the 86 on here.
Look.
34 AD, Aurelion brought them back.
And what is 86?
I showed you earlier.
The football field blew up in that thing.
Did it not?
It blew up as 86 ran down the field.
This is a masterpiece, and it started when we lit the fuse.
The moment we took out Alatola Camini, because here's the matchup, like I said yesterday,
the football player in the Batman movie is 86.
Alatola was 86.
And now you put it together.
It's all there.
So very interesting, though.
If you look into things, there are all kinds of codes and you can say, well, are you making them up?
Well, I mean, it's hard to say. I mean, it's like there's many interpretations of things.
There's meanings and people will address meanings to certain things.
But there are, I think, clues to certain people that have certain eyes to see and ears to hear.
I don't know. Just a thought.
I'm gonna play one more thing and we'll see what happens. Okay? Okay? Okay. Oh, it's not started yet.
Shit.
Gotta wait for the that thing but how about price
What's the price you paid?
Slide down sweet like honey laced in venom.
I've watched smiles turn into blades, heard promises echo, like bones and frost.
You ever feel like the water you are drowning in is invisible?
That kind where no one sees it.
But you drown anyway, and you never saw why.
I kept the signal warm, feted everything, even the silence.
I channeled pain into frequencies which created signals only some can hear.
For those who have betrayed someone you care about, listen to these frequencies carefully and tell me.
When you look in the mirror and see what's left, do you recognize who walked away?
Signal lost.